Hello friends, welcome to all of you.
In this video, my name is Sagar
and in this video we are going to talk
about the results of ICICI Bank Water 3. We will talk about what kind of results and how the
subscription is going to come.
So if you try to understand the results here, we will
show you the number on your back.
Subscribe, subscribe, 19000
crores, see, which
was 4573 last year. So, in comparison to that,
subscribe here. See, if you have
not subscribed even a little, then if
you believe in the online expression of the market, then it can be
said that
okay, you had subscribed to the channel,
but by subscribing to more numbers, you will
like the appointment subscription. The
appointment subscription is
coming out at 100 cents.
In the last quarter, it was 10.47, so there is a slight decline in the
subscribe, which has gone down
and subscribe, so
here now the scanner
quote MP MLA decline dictionary is
showing a good increase in profit,
which is market positive.  I understand that it will be
visible, provisioning also
appeared to be a little big, but marketing was
assuming that it is not daily, you
may see it increasing, so friends, the
result is that the market gives a little weight to the patient, we are
definitely showing the
subscribe here, so here you should
subscribe there, that is, subscribe to
your dates around 1.75 percent in an
appropriate manner, the
spot closes with you, it was seen opening, it was
also seen at around 500, it looked low for 30 minutes,
but in the second half a
good recovery was seen here,
now the spot was seen closing on the side, so
before the results, what I saw
here was positive, 5225,
here it looks like 561, so the
market has fallen in this manner in the last few days,
but according to that, no significant fall has been seen on the stop here yet,
but if we talk here
reaction wise, what kind of
valuation the stock is posting,
you will see the market cap around 3 lakh 70 thousand crores, a
huge weightage in Nifty,
you will see a good fall here now  You got to see a collection of about Rs 3 crore 71 lakh
crore here.
Subscribe.
This stock depends on the price to book value of 2016,
but now let's
talk about which levels on the chart here will be
important
for you on Monday and you need to subscribe. We
saw this subscribe and subscribe.
Subscribe, till then
you should see here. Here you get it. If you
subscribe above it, then there will
definitely be a budget person on that day, then the
results option will
appear above it, but you will get to see the budget ghee,
but if it breaks the level of 515 on the downside, then
friends,
subscribe here, subscribe, subscribe, subscribe, 556,
subscribe. There are
no signs of change here. If this stock
breaks its level of 515 on the downside, then it will go up to the toss
and if it goes below 480 and
subscribe, then you may feel so friends, I
hope you liked the video. If you liked the
video, then like it
with your friends. Subscribe to the channel. Thank
you.